https://gameglance.com/privacy-policy/

GAMEGLANCE
GamingNewsAugmented RealityGoogle StadiaMacNintendo SwitchNintendo Switch LitePCPS4PS5Super NES ClassicVirtual RealityXbox One SXbox One XAppsGadgetsMobile PhonesSecurityTelevisionsWatchesTechAnnouncementsBuying GuidesEnterpriseEventsIndustry NewsRumorsStartupsGearAccessoriesAudioHardwareReviewsGameGlance provides concise reviews and news of gadgets and gaming in a easy to read 2-minute format. We provide a quick glance and leave the rest up to you.MorePRIVACYSUBMITWork @ GameGlanceCategoriesAccessoriesAnnouncementsAppsAudioEnterpriseEventsGadgetsGamingGearHardwareIndustry NewsMobile PhonesNewsNintendo SwitchPCPS4PS5ReviewsRumorsSecurityStartupsTechTelevisionsUncategorizedWatchesXbox One SXbox One XWho we areOur website address is: https://gameglance.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect it>CommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.>MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact forms>CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.>Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.>AnalyticsWe may also use third parties to serve ads on the Service. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit the Service (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number), unless hashed or otherwise converted to non-PII. They do this by using cookies, clear gifs or other Tracking Technologies (defined below). Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of the Service and the other sites and services tracked by these third parties (“Interest-based Advertising”). We are not responsible for Tracking Technologies in or related to third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology.You may choose whether to receive some Interest-based Advertising by submitting opt-outs. One of the third party ad servers that delivers Interest-based Advertising to you is Doubleclick. For Doubleclick’s Privacy Policy, click here. Some of the other advertisers and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and third parties may participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. To learn more about how you can exercise certain choices regarding Interest-based Advertising, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, and http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices for information on the DAA’s opt-out program for mobile apps. Some of these companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To learn more about the NAI and your opt-out options for their members, see http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. Please be aware that, even if you are able to opt out of certain kinds of Interest-based Advertising, you may continue to receive other types of ads. Opting out only means that those selected members should no longer deliver certain Interest-based Advertising to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads (e.g., from other ad networks). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit these opt-out webpages, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or web browsers or use a non-browser-based method of access (e.g., mobile app), your NAI / DAA browser-based opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. We support the ad industry’s 2009 Self-regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising (https://www.iab.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/ven-principles-07-01-09.pdf) and expect that ad networks Company directly engages to serve you Interest-based Advertising will do so as well, though we cannot guaranty their compliance. We are not responsible for effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their programs.GameGlance may use Google Analytics, Adobe Analytics or other service providers for analytics services. These analytics services may use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to help us analyze Service users and how they use the Service. Information generated by these services (e.g., your IP address and other usage information) may be transmitted to and stored by these service providers on servers in the U.S. (or elsewhere) and these service providers may use this information for purposes such as evaluating your use of the Service, compiling statistic reports on the Service’s activity, and providing other services relating to Service activity and other Internet usage. You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Google Analytics by going to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout or downloading the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. You may exercise choices regarding the use of cookies from Adobe Analytics by going to http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html under the section labeled “Tell our customers not to measure your use of their websites or tailor their online ads for you.”Who we share your data withGameGlance may share your PII for any purposes and circumstances not prohibited by applicable law or inconsistent with the applicable Privacy Policy or any statement made by us to you in writing at the time of collection, including without limitation:We may share your PII with our affiliates, our technical consultants, auditors and other third parties who act on our behalf, for example, to make the Service available, enhance functionality, or provide services related to the Service or fulfillment of subscriptions or orders for any of our publications or other products and services (such as sending emails, processing credit cards, fulfilling subscriptions and other orders, providing customer service, and performing data-, information technology-, or marketing-related services), and/or who assist us in producing, delivering, billing, collecting payment for, renewing and otherwise managing content, samples, products, and gifts and prizes.We may make your PII, along with certain other information about you (such as your interest in particular health or lifestyle topics or your subscription information), available to third parties for the purpose of offering products and services that may interest you, unless you opt out of such information sharing. (See the sections below entitled “Notice of Your Choices about Our Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information” and “Notice to California Customers – Your California Privacy Rights” on opting out of information sharing).We may transfer your PII and other information in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.We will consider, and may release, PII to third parties: to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of Company, our agents, customers, members, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use, or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of Company employees, customers, or any person.We may also provide aggregate statistics and de-identified data about our customers, which we treat as non-PII as permitted by applicable law, including data about traffic patterns and related site information, to third parties for their own purposes, including statistical analysis. For instance, we and third parties may convert your PII to a unique identifier, such as through hashing (which we treat as non-PII as permitted by applicable law), and we and third parties may use and share that data as permitted by applicable law, including to match data attributes to and from other data sources. Any such third party activities are subject to their privacy policies and practices.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.International VisitorsFor additional information about our privacy practices and additional rights you may have please click on the appropriate link for your jurisdiction:Australiahttps://privacy.cbs/www.youronlinechoices.com.auCanadahttps://www.priv.gc.ca/en/privacy-topics/privacy-laws-in-canada/the-personal-information-protection-and-electronic-documents-act-pipeda/The European Unionhttps://gdpr-info.eu/Additional informationHow we protect your dataWe take appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that the information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used. We protect your information in accordance with the IT Security Policy of our CRM service provider – Salesforce.We use a secure service when you make a payment through our website, via a virtual gateway operated by PayPal. Our online payment system is Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard compliant.You should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and although we will do our best to protect your personal data we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features such as encryption to try to prevent unauthorized access.What data breach procedures we have in placeUpon being notified of a (suspected or confirmed) data breach, the Data Breach Team should immediately activate the data breach & response plan.GameGlances’ data breach management and response plan is:Confirm the BreachContain the BreachAssess Risks and ImpactReport the IncidentEvaluate the Response & Recovery to Prevent Future BreachesCONFIRM THE BREACHThe Data Breach Team (DBT) should act as soon as it is aware of a data breach. Where possible, it should first confirm that the data breach has occurred. It may make sense for the DBT to proceed Contain the Breach on the basis of an unconfirmed reported data breach, depending on the likelihood of the severity of risk.CONTAIN THE BREACHThe DBT should consider the following measures to Contain the Breach, where applicable:Shut down the compromised system that led to the data breach.Establish whether steps can be taken to recover lost data and limit any damage caused by the breach. (eg: remotely disabling / wiping a lost notebook containing personal data of individuals.)Prevent further unauthorized access to the system.Reset passwords if accounts and / or passwords have been compromised.Isolate the causes of the data breach in the system, and where applicable, change the access rights to the compromised system and remove external connections to the system.ASSESS RISKS AND IMPACTKnowing the risks and impact of data breaches will help GameGlance determine whether there could be serious consequences to affected individuals, as well as the steps necessary to notify the individuals affected.Contact informationGameGlance Media Corp.1 Silom StreetSuite 101Bangkok, Thailand 10120privacy@gameglance.com Search for:
Search The Last Five
1
Sony rolls out their new redesigned PlayStation App for PS4 and PS5October 29, 2020
2
CD Projekt Red’s CyberPunk 2077 release pushed back to December 10October 28, 2020
3
Video game prices set to skyrocket to new heightsOctober 27, 2020
4
Atari VCS game console. An icon reimagined.October 25, 2020
5
Xbox Series X release expected in November 2020July 26, 2020Socialize with us
CategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryAccessories  (2)Announcements  (13)Apps  (1)Audio  (2)Enterprise  (1)Events  (2)Gadgets  (6)Gaming  (29)Gear  (6)Hardware  (2)Industry News  (16)Mobile Phones  (2)News  (11)Nintendo Switch  (1)PC  (11)PS4  (10)PS5  (11)Reviews  (3)Rumors  (6)Security  (1)Startups  (1)Tech  (22)Televisions  (2)Uncategorized  (3)Watches  (1)Xbox One S  (2)Xbox One X  (8)
Search for:
Search Input your search keywords and press Enter.Join Our Newsletter
Subscribe
By checking this box, you confirm that you have read and are agreeing to our terms of use regarding the storage of the data submitted through this form.
